{
    "id": "92c9a88e376a412fb7a281b70bed5d1f",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is ………………….. to refuse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a polite person",
                "a too polite person",
                "too polite a person"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………….. as you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a voice as good",
                "as good a voice",
                "a good voice"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t afford to buy ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that big a home",
                "that a big home"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… is he?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How good a singer",
                "How a good singer",
                "How good singer"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………, you are wrong.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "According to me",
                "In my opinion",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am interested ………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to learn painting",
                "in learning to paint",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important that everybody ………………….. comfortable.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "feels",
                "should feel"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She smiled ………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "friendly",
                "in a friendly way"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ball hit me ………………….. on the nose.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "right",
                "rightly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fear",
                "be afraid"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}